{
    "subject": "Lucas_Belvaux",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Rapt__2009_film_",
    "human_readable": "Lucas Belvaux directed the film Rapt (2009).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8369405269622803,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Lucas Belvaux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8324582576751709,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Lucas Belvaux."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7348731756210327,
            "question": "Is Lucas Belvaux a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7324084639549255,
            "question": "Who directed the film Rapt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7235950231552124,
            "question": "What other films has Lucas Belvaux directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5350803732872009,
            "question": "What year was the film Rapt released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35596081614494324,
            "question": "Can you provide information about the plot of Rapt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32386353611946106,
            "question": "What genre is the film Rapt likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30315521359443665,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with the film Rapt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1588016152381897,
            "question": "Would you recommend watching Rapt?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lucas Belvaux directed the film Rapt (2009).",
            "html": "yago_10404_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with the film Rapt?",
            "html": "yago_10404_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Rapt likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_10404_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide information about the plot of Rapt?",
            "html": "yago_10404_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10404_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Lucas Belvaux directed the film Rapt (2009)\". Multiple entries mention Lucas Belvaux as the director of the film \"Rapt\", confirming this triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}